https://davincibridal.com/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
Davincibridal.com Respects Your PrivacyAny personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of davincibridal.com.
Credit Card DetailsDavincibridal.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on davincibridal.com.
External SitesDavincibridal.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
CookiesA "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows greatpricemovers.com to recognize you each time you visit this site (customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and davincibridal.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The InternetWhile we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to davincibridal.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through davincibridal.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
For any other information email webmaster.
Yes! I want exclusive eccess to the hottest bridal tips, trends and ideas from DaVinci Bridal via email.
Create account
×
Sign In
(Retailer? Login Here)
Email
Password
Forgot password?
Keep me logged in
Sign in
Sign in with Facebook
Create an account
Note:
Your account will work across all Emme websites,
including:
DaVinciBridal.com,
Your form has been submitted successfully.
